Guide to the Casey Recordings, 1944-1985 CASEY.2001
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Casey Recordings
1944-1985
1947-1948
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Casey, Rosemary
CASEY.2001
5 Linear Feet (197 albums)
The Casey Recordings are a collection of LPs from RCA mostly dating from around the late 1940's. They were donated to the collection by Rosemary Casey, who worked for RCA at that time creating their catalogue as well as writing liner notes for the records. This collection includes mostly classical and opera recordings. Also included are many Christmas, International, and even some Test Pressings.
Acquisition Information
This collection was gifted by Rosemary Casey to the Center for American Music Stephen Foster Hall Archives in 2001.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into nine series; each series is broken into item level descriptions for each LP.
Series I. Christmas
Series II. Classical
Series III. Folk
Series IV. International
Series V. Jazz
Series VI. Musical
Series VII. Popular
Series VIII. Spoken
Series IX. Test Pressings
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Scope and Content Notes
The Casey Recordings are housed in individual record sleeves. Most of the sleeves are the original record album covers. The Test Pressings and a few other LPs are housed in archival quality generic record sleeves. The records are housed standing vertically on the shelf space so as to reduce wear and warping of the LPs. Each series in this collection consists of individual LPs with various artists.
Biography
Rosemary Casey, formerly Rosemary McHenry, was born on May 13, 1923 in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. She attended parochial schools as a child and West Catholic High School as a teenager. After graduating from high school, Mrs. Casey attended The University of Pennsylvania where she earned two degrees: a Bachelor of Arts in Music and a Bachelor of Arts in Psychology.
In 1944, Mrs. Casey went for an interview with an agency and landed a job at RCA Victor in the catalog department. Working from the eighth floor of the Camden office in New York, Mrs. Casey was instrumental in compiling one of the most comprehensive LP catalogues in RCA's history: the RCA Victor Red Seal Catalogue. She was also responsible for many attributed and some unattributed liner notes for the recordings. She was a pioneer in the area of women in the work place as she did not work in a traditionally female role such as a secretary. While at RCA, Mrs. Casey acquired a modest collection of LPs, some of which were rare test pressings.
Mrs. Casey worked at RCA Victor until 1949 when the edition of the Red Seal Catalog was complete. She married shortly after leaving RCA.
Phonograph records; Test pressings (Sound recordings) -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Sound recordings -- Collectors and collecting -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Sound recording libraries -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Music; RCA Manufacturing Company, inc; RCA-Victor Company, inc
- Christmas, 1968, 1973; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series consists of four albums. These albums showcase a range of Christmas songs and compositions song by a variety of popular artists.
  - The Perry Como Christmas Album, 1968 (Record CAS CHR 0001)
    This album consists of one disc with two sides. Side(A)includes Christmas Eve; Do You Hear What I Hear; Christ is Born; The Little Drummer Boy; There Is No Christmas Like a Home Christmas; O Holy Night. Side (B) includes Carol Medley: Caroling, Caroling-The First Noel-Hark! The Herald Angels Sing-Silent Night; Silver Bells; Toyland; Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas; Ave Maria.
  - Merry Christmas: Bing Crosby (Record CAS CHR 0002)
    This album consists of one disc with two sides. Side (A) includes Silent Night; Adeste Fidelis; White Christmas; God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen; Faith of Our Fathers; I'll Be Home for Christmas (If Only in My Dreams). Side (B) includes Jingle Bells; Santa Claus is Coming to Town; Silver Bells; It's Beginning to Look a Lot Like Christmas; Christmas in Killarney; Mele Kalikimaka (Merry Christmas).
  - Merry Christmas: Johnny Mathis (Record CAS CHR 0003)
    This album consists of one disc with two sides. Side (A) includes Winter Wonderland; The Christmas Song; Sleigh Ride; Blue Christmas; I'll Be Home for Christmas; White Christmas. Side (B) includes O Holy Night; What Child is This? (Greensleeves); The First Noel; Silver Bells; It Came Upon the Midnight Clear; Silent Night, Holy Night.
  - The Best of Bing Crosby; Christmas Hymns and Carols, 1973 (Record CAS CHR 0004)
    This album consists of 5 discs, 4 of which have two sides. The first disc only has one side (B) and includes Dear Hearts and Gentle People; Galway Bay; In the Cool, Cool, Cool of the Evening; Too-ra-loo-ra-loo-ral (That's an Irish Lullabye); Sam's Song (The Happy Tune); Now is the Hour (Maori Farewell Song).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes (A) Joy to the World (B) It Came upon a Midnight Clear (C) Angels We Have Heard on High. Side (B) includes (A) O Come, O Come, Emanuel (B) O Little Town of Bethlehem (C) Silent Night.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes (A) O Come All Ye Faithful (Adeste Fideles) (B) Luther's Cradle Hymn (Away in the Manger) (C) God Rest You Merry Gentlemen. Side (B) includes (A) We Three Kings (B) The First Noel (C) Hark! The Herald Angels Sing.
    Disc 4 side (A) includes (A) Shepherd's Carol (Carol from the Suffolk Harmony, 1786) (B) Coventry Carol (C) Patapan. Side (B) includes (A) My Dancing Day (B) I Wonder as I Wander (C) Bring a Torch, Jeanette, Isabella.
    Disc 5 side (A) includes (A) Carol of the Bells (B) Lo, How a Rose E'er Blooming (C) Go Tell it on the Mountain. Side (B) includes (A) I Sing of a Maiden (B) Echo Hymn (C) Wassail Song (D) Deck the Halls with Boughs of Holly. There are also program notes by Dexter, Jr., Dave on album cover and the Album is a duplicate of John Harvith 2160-2167. Notes by David Hall
- Folk, III.
  This series consists of two albums. These albums represent the American Popular music of Folk in which there are no clear composers for these songs, only arrangers and performers.
  - Glenn, Wilfred (bass) with orchestra; Down Deep With the Cellar; The Monarch of the Woods (Record CAS FLK 0001)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Down Deep With the Cellar. Side (B) The Monarch of the Woods.
  - Werrenrath, Reinald (baritone) with orchestra; Drink to Me Only With Thine Eyes; My Lovely Celia (Record CAS FLK 0002)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Drink to Me Only With Thine Eyes. Side (B) includes My Lovely Celia. The album sold for $1 in US.
- International, 1944, 1977, 1982, 1985; IV.
  This series consists of eight albums. These albums repesent songs from other countries with the bulk being from Ireland.
  - Songs of Lidice: Jarmila Novotna, soprano; Jan Masaryk at the piano (Record CAS INT 0001)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes (A) Prečos Nám Neprišiel (B) Zelení Hajové (C) Šly Panenky Silnicí. Side (B) includes (A) Ach Synku, Synku (B) Zdálo se mi, Má Panenko.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes (A) Kto Má Počernú Galánku (B) Horo, Horo Vysoká Jsi!. Side (B) includes (A) Láska Bože Laská (B) Teče Voda Teče (C) Andulko, Mé Dítê.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes (A) Ach Není Tu Není (B) Pod Tým Naší m Okienečkom. Side (B) includes (A) Dobrú Noc (B) Koupím Já Si Koné Vraný (C) Umrem, Umrem. This album also includes includes diatribe against Hitler on inside cover and a summary of songs.
  - Irish Sing-Along: The Bill Shepherd Singers (Record CAS INT 0002)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes When Irish Eyes Are Smiling; The Rose of Tralee; Kerry Dance; A Little Bit of Heaven (Shure They Call It Ireland); I'll Take You Home Again Kathleen; Shenanigans (Two of Irish).
    Side (B) includes Too-ra-loo-ra-loo-ral (That's An Irish Lullaby); Mother Machree; Come Back to Erin; The Girl I Left Behind Me; Molly Malone; Christmas in Killarney. This album also includes full lyrics on cover as well as a Decca catalog on sleeve.
  - La Marseillaise, 1944 (Record CAS INT 0003)
    This album consists of 1 one-sided disc. This album includes La Marseillaise.
  - The Great John McCormack (Record CAS INT 0004)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes The Kerry Dance; Kashmiri Song; Down by the Sally Gardens; Jesu, Joy of Man's Desiring; Trees; Song to the Seals. Side (B) includes Mighty Lak' a Rose; Bantry Bay; Smilin' Through; Plaisir D'Amour; So Deep is the Night; God Keep You Is My Prayer.
  - Ireland's John MacNally, Vol. 2, 1985 (Record CAS INT 0005)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Are You Right There Michael?; Macushla; The Croppy Boy; Mother Machree; Sally Broome; Boolavogue; Come Back Paddy Reilly; Irish Trilogy (Isle of Innistree; Come Back to Erin; A Nation Once Again).
    Side (B) includes Morning Has Broken; How Great Thou Art; Holy City (Jerusalem); I'll Walk With God; Bless This House; The Bells of St. Mary's; Ave Maria; May Each Day. This album's cover is autographed by the performer.
  - "The Best of Irish Humor", 1977 (Record CAS INT 0006)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Both sides include "The Best of Irish Humor." This album also includes a review by Byrge, Gay on album cover.
  - "We Irish talk like that", 1982 (Record CAS INT 0007)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Both sides includes "We Irish talk like that." This album also includes a review by Andrew, Eamonn on album cover.
  - Fiesta en San Juan (Holiday in San Juan) (Record CAS INT 0008)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes En Mi Viejo San Juan (bolero); Sara (danza); En La Calle De La Tanca; Recuerdos (danza); Plenas Del Viejo San Juan. Side (B) includes Tu Risa (vals); Amparo (danza); Que Linda Eres (bolero); Quejas Del Alma (danza); Conversación (danza). This album also includes information in Spanish and English on album cover.
- Jazz, 1956; V.
  This series consists of one album. This album showcases The American Popular music of Jazz.
  - The Magic Horn-George Wein, 1956 (Record CAS JAZ 0001)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes The Magic Horn; Sugar; Struttin' with Some Barbecue; Ain't Gonna Give Nobody None of My Jellyroll. Side (B) includes A Monday Date; Squeeze Me; On the Sunny Side of the Street; Loveless Love; Dippermouth Blues.
- Musical, 1962, 1973; VI.
  This series consists of four albums. These albums represent musical soundtracks from various stage shows and movies.
  - Shore, Dinah (voice) with Sack, Albert (conductor) and orchestra; Love Walked In; Someone to Watch Over Me (Record CAS MUS 0001)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Love Walked In. Side (B) includes Someone to Watch Over Me. This album is part of a larger set.
  - Camelot (Lerner and Lowe): Original Broadway Cast, 1973 (Record CAS MUS 0002)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Overture; I Wonder What the King is Doing Tonight; The Simple Joys of Maidenhood; Camelot; Follow Me; The Lusty Month of May; C'est Moi; Then You May Take Me to the Fair; How to Handle a Woman.
    Side (B) includes If Ever I Would Leave You; Parade; Before I Gaze at You Again; The Seavenly Deadly Virtues; What Do the Simple Folk Do?; Fie on Goodness!; I Loved You Once In Silence; Guenevere; Camelot-reprise. Record is still in unopened packaging. Cover includes plot summary.
  - Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Presents a Joe Pasternak Production: "Billy Rose's Jumbo", 1962 (Record CAS MUS 0003)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes The Circus on Parade; Over and Over Again; Why Can't I?; This Can't Be Love. Side (B) includes The Most Beautiful Girl in the World; My Romance; The Most Beautiful Girl in the World-Reprise; Little Girl Blue; Sawdust, Spangles and Dreams-Finale. Cover includes plot summary and brief biographies of the singers.
  - Herman Levin presents Rex Harrison/Julie Andrews: "My Fair Lady" (Record CAS MUS 0004)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Overture; Why Can't the English?; Wouldn't it Be Loverly?; With a Little Bit of Luck; I'm an Ordinary Man; Just You Wait; The Rain in Spain; I Could Have Danced All Night.
    Side (B) includes Ascot Gavotte; On the Street Where You Live; You Did It; Show Me; Get Me to the Church on Time; A Hymn to Him; Without You; I've Grown Accustomed to Her Face; Finale. This album includes a plot summary on cover.
- Popular, 1966, 1969, 1972-1974, 1979; VII.
  This series consists of 19 albums. These albums represnt American Popular music from the 1960's and 1970's.
  - Artie Shaw and His Orchestra; I'll Never Be the Same (foxtrot); 'S Wonderful (foxtrot) (Record CAS POP 0001)
    This album cosists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes I'll Never Be the Same (foxtrot). Side (B) includes 'S Wonderful (foxtrot). The record is chipped.
  - Beneke, Tex (voice and conductor) with the Miller Orchestra, Stevens, Gary and the Mello Larks (voice); Hoodle Addle; Anniversary Song (based on a theme by Ivanovich) (Record CAS POP 0002)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Hoodle Addle. Side (B) includes Anniversary Song (based on a theme by Ivanovich).
  - One Billion Records: Commemorating an Achievement for Music Lovers (Record CAS POP 0003)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Tell Me Pretty Maiden and was recorded January 21, 1901 and is known as the "Oldest Victor 'Master' Record". Side (B) includes Semper Fidelis and was recorded in 1946.
  - Everybody Loves a Parade: The American Concert and Marching Band (Record CAS POP 0004)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes John Kennedy; Deep in the Heart of Texas; Stars & Strips Foerver; Triumphal March; March of the Slaves; Triumphal March of Caesar's Legions; The Conqueror; The Minstrel boy; March of the Toreadors; Medley: Romeo & Juliet, March from the "Nutcracker Suite"; L'Arlesienne Fantasy.
    Side (B) includes Colonel Bogey March (From "Bridge on the River Kwai"); U.S. Field Artillery; American Patrol; Semper Fidelis; National Emblem; El Capitan; Washington Post March; The Thunderer; Navaraisse (from "El Cid"); Prelude & Toreador Song (From "Carmen").
  - The Best of Bing Crosby, 1973 (Record CAS POP 0005)
    This album consists of 2 discs. Disc 1 has 2 sides while disc 2 is one-sided. Disc 1 side (A) includes Where the Blue of the Night Meets the Gold of the Day; Swinging on a Star; June in January; You are My Sunshine; It's Been a Long, Long Time; MacNamara's Band.
    Side (B) includes The One Rose (That's Left in My Heart); Sweet Leilani; I'm an Old Cowhand (From The Rio Grande); It's Easy to Remember; Pennies From Heaven; Don't Fence Me In.
    Disc 2 includes Sunshine Cake; I Can't Begin to Tell You; Mexicali Rose; The Whiffenpoof Song; Play a Simple Melody; White Christmas. The album also includes program notes by Dexter, Jr., Dave on album cover.
  - The Charm of the Old Music Box (Record CAS POP 0006)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Silent Night; Star of the East; Angel's Serenade; Oh, How Joyfully (O Sanctissima); O Come All Ye Faithful (Adeste Fidelis); Come Hither Ye Childer (Ihr Kinderlein Kommet); O, Tannenbaum; First Noel; Hark the Herald Angels Sing; Ave Maria.
    Side (B) includes Carnival of Venice; Magic Flute; El Puritana; Pride of the Ball; Glow Worm; Tyrolean and His Child (Der Tiroler Und Sein Kind); Forsaken, Forsaken (Verlassen, Verlassen); Ben Bolt; Brahms' Lullaby; La Traviata (The Drinking Song); Wedding of the Winds. This album's cover includes histories of the music boxes.
  - Shillelaghs and Shamrocks: Bing Crosby, 1973 (Record CAS POP 0007)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes MacNamara's Band; Dear Old Donegal; Who Threw the Overalls in Mrs. Murphy's Chowder?; It's the Same old Shillelagh; Two Shillelagh O'Sullivan; The Donovans.
    Side (B) includes Did Your Mother Come from Ireland?; Where the River Shannon Flows; The Rose of Tralee; When Irish Eyes Are Smiling; With My Shillelagh Under My Arm; St. Patrick's Day Parade.
  - Carpenters: The Singles 1969-1973 (Record CAS POP 0008)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes We've Only Just Begun; Top of the World; Ticket to Ride; Superstar; Rainy Day and Mondays; Goodbye to Love. Side (B) includes Yesterday Once More; It's Going to Take Some Time; Sing; For All We Know; Hurting Each Other; (They Long To Be) Close To You). This album also includes booklet with commentary and lyrics.
  - Have You Met Miss Carroll? (Record CAS POP 0009)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Everything I've Got Belongs to You; It's All Right with Me; Happiness is a Thing Called Joe; Almost Like Being in Love; Love Is a Simple Thing; Get Happy.
    Side (B) includes Two Ladies in de Shade of de Banana Tree; My Heart Belongs to Daddy; You're Mine; Have You Met Miss Jones; I'm Glad There Is You; Barbara's Carol. This album also includes biography of Carroll on cover.
  - Jim Croce "Photographs and Memories": His Greatest Hits, 1974 (Record CAS POP 0010)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Bad, Bad Leroy Brown; Operator (That's Not The Way It Feels); Photographs and Memories; Rapid Roy (The Stock Car Boy); Time in a Bottle; New York's Not My Home; Workin' at the Car Wash Blues.
    Side (B) includes I Got a Name (From the film "The Last American Hero"); I'll Have to Say I Love You in a Song; You Don't Mess Around with Jim; Lover's Cross; One Less Set of Footsteps; These Dreams; Roller Derby Queen. This album also includes commentary by Josh Mills on sleeve.
  - Disco Nights: Non-Stop Original Disco Hits, 1979 (Record CAS POP 0011)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Boogie Oogie Oogie; Macho Man; You an I; Do You Feel All Right; You Got Me Running; Shadow Dancing; Disco (Disco Heat). Side (B) includes I Love the Nightlife (Disco 'Round); Don't Hold Back; Shame; You Should Do It; Get Off; Love Won't Be Denied; Think It Over.
  - Marching Along Together…The Goldman Band (Record CAS POP 0012)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Semper Fidelis; The Army Air Cops; Anchors Aweigh; Sabre and Spurs; The Army's Always There; The Marines' Hymn. Side (B) includes The Official West Point March; Semper Paratus; The U.S. Field Artillery March; On, Brave Old Army Team; America the Beautiful; Dixie; America; The Star Spangled Banner.
  - Al Martino: Daddy's Little Girl (Record CAS POP 0013)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Daddy's Little Girl; Mary in the Morning; The Wheel of Hurt; My Cup Runneth Over; This is My Song; She'll Always Love You. Side (B) includes Born Free; I Love You and You Love Me; Once Upon a Time; Somewhere in this World; A Woman in Love.
  - Frank Sinatra's Great Hits-Vol. II, 1972 (Record CAS POP 0014)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes My Way; A Man Alone; Cycles; Bein' Green; Love's Been Good to Me; I'm Not Afraid. Side (B) includes Goin' Out of My Head; What's Now is Now; Star!; The September of My Years.
  - Catch Bull at Four, 1972 (Record CAS POP 0015)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Sitting; Boy With a Moon & Star on His Head; Angelsea; Silent Sunlight; Can't Keep It In. Side (B) includes 18th Avenue; Freezing Steel; O Caritas; Sweet Scarlet; Ruins.
  - The Supremes A'Go-Go, 1966 (Record CAS POP 0016)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Love is Like an Itching in My Heart; This Old Heart of Mine (Is Weak for You); You Can't Hurry Love; Shake Me, Wake Me (When It's Over); Baby I Need Your Loving; These Boots Are Made for Walking.
    Side (B) includes I Can't Help Myself; Get Ready; Put Yourself in My Place; Money (That's What I Want); Come and Get These Memories; Hang On Sloopy.
  - James Taylor: Sweet Baby James (Record CAS POP 0017)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Sweet Baby James; Lo and Behold; Sunny Skies; Steamroller; Country Road; Oh, Susanna. Side (B) includes Fire and Rain; Blossom; Anywhere Like Heaven; Oh Baby, Don't You Loose Your Lip On Me; Suite for 20 G. This album also includes poster with lyrics on the reverse.
  - Up Tight on Fifth Avenue (Record CAS POP 0018)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Turn-Down Day; Hungry; Cry Like a Baby; By the Time I Get to Phoenix; Don't You Care. Side (B) includes Land of 1000 Dances; Tighten Up; Hang On Sloopy; When a Man Loves a Woman; I Think We're Alone Now.
  - Dionne Warwick's Greatest Motion Picture Hits, 1969 (Record CAS POP 0019)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes The Look of Love; Alfie; Valley of the Dolls; People; A House is Not a Home; Wives and Lovers. Side (B) includes The April Fools; Slaves; One Hand, One Heart; Here I Am; As Long as He Needs Me; Somewhere.
- Spoken, VIII.
  This series consists of one album. This album is a recording of the reading aloud of Walt Whitman's poetry.
  - Ralph Bellamy in Walt Whitman's Immortal "Leaves of Grass" (Excerpts) (Record CAS SPK 0001)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Introduction; To a Certain Civilian; I Think I Could Turn and Live with Animals; To the Man-of-War Bird; For You O Democracy. Side (B) includes Vigil Strange I Kept on the Field One Night; Long, Too Long America; Over the Carnage Rose Prophectic a Voice.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes O Star of France; To a Foil'd European Revolutionaire. Side (B) includes Europe; France; A Broadway Pageant.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Years of the Modern; I Was Looking a Long While; Passage to India. Side (B) includes By Blue Ontario's Shore.
    Disc 4 side (A) includes So Long! Side (B) includes Song of the Open Road. The first disc is chipped but the chip is with teh record in the sleeve. This album also includes text inside album cover.
- Test Pressings, 1947-1948; IX.
  This series consists of 49 albums. These albums are test pressings from the RCA Victor recording studios during the late 1940's. Much of the content of these recordings is unknown due to fading or improper labeling.
  - Italian Symphony [?], 1948 (Record CAS TST 0001)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing and includes Italian Symphony [?]. This album's original sleeve indicates "Mendel. Ital." Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0002)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing with unknown content. Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Träumerei, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0003)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Träumerei.
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0004)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing with unkown content. Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - A Cantos for a Sabbath, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0005)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes A Cantos for a Sabbath. Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - La Guide Haleuy [?], 1948 (Record CAS TST 0006)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes La Guide Haleuy [?]. Original sleeve inside new sleeve. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record Cas TST 0007)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing with unknown content. Original sleeve inside new sleeve. Appears to be a duplicate of RC 0420.
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0008)
  - [?] No. 27; Mozart, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0009)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Mozart's No. 27[?]. Original sleeve inside new sleeve. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - [?] No. 27; Mozart, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0010)